<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Furniture</string>
    <string name="furnature1">Newport Sofa</string>
    <string name="furnature2">Coffee Table</string>
    <string name="furnature3">Parker Bed</string>
    <string name="furnature4">Storage Media</string>
    <string name="furnature5">Shelf Desk</string>

    <string name="peice1">SAR 10,500.00</string>
    <string name="peice2">SAR 3,150.00</string>
    <string name="peice3">SAR 8,675.00</string>
    <string name="peice4">SAR 7,650.00</string>
    <string name="peice5">SAR 1,545.00</string>


    <string name="des1">Casual and coastal-inspired, our Newport Sofa boasts clean lines and deep seats with an airy but durable kiln-dried wooden platform.</string>
    <string name="des2">Our two-tiered Art Display Coffee Table doubles down on mid-century style and storage space with its durable, tempered glass top and sophisticated finish. An open shelf offers room for baskets and your favorite reads.</string>
    <string name="des3">Our Parker Collection is all about understated elegance, featuring modern shapes, quality materials and subtle tailored touches. Its headboard features a single channel stitch up top and comes covered in your choice of fabric. Each is Contract Grade, meaning it is extra durable.</string>
    <string name="des4">Made from richly-grained solid mango wood and lofted on blackened steel legs, our Industrial Storage Media Console brings an earthy charm to the bare-bones media console. In a grand 80-inch size, it features four drawers and two open shelves—that means even more space to store books, cable boxes and other electronics.</string>
    <string name="des5">Designed with smaller spaces in mind, our Ladder Shelf Desk has a compact footprint and comes at a great value. It fits in with an eclectic mix of bedroom or living room styles.</string>


    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="min">-</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>


</resources>